I'm so over this. It's way too hot. Kojo, aren't you dying to go and cool off somewhere?
I wouldn't mind.
Hello and welcome.
Oh wow, I've never been to a manga cafe before.
Aw, you poor thing. Well, I highly recommend them. It's always nice and cool inside, there's food and drinks, and of course, you can read anything you want.
But, it's pretty much paradise.
Oh, sounds great. Except... we're so close!
I love how much room there is to stretch your legs!
I... I, uh...
I lost it.
Thank you.
I was just wondering.
Check it out. You hungry?
Huh? Everything on this menu is gigantic!
I almost forgot I brought this one with me.
I'm giving it a hardcore wreck. You have to read it.
I'm a mega best-selling high school student, light novel author that has a succubus thirsting for me every night and I don't know what to do.
Were all of those words part of the title?
Or Suck-Eye Decay. Four-panel slice of life.
What's a slice of life?
Hmm, it's like when nothing really happens, but that's what's so great about it. Just a nice, tranquil story with cherries on top.
So the characters just do normal things and people like to read about that?
Yeah, exactly right. Slice of life stuff is all warm and fuzzy, so it makes for great bedtime reading.
In Suck-Eye Decay, the main guy Kaname stays up all night writing light novels, so like he never gets any rest.
Then Liz, who's a succubus, makes it her mission to try to get him to sleep.
Look how cute her mini pigtails are!
That's like a ginormous weakness of mine. I always fall for characters who have them.
You mean her hairstyle?
That's why I have such a crush on Juju! I seriously want to cosplay Liz something fierce! I love her so hard! I mean, look at her! She is a dwarves!
Veronica does show a lot of skin. I promise to be more sensitive when I pick the next character.
At least there's more to this cosplay than Veronica's.
Not saying I'd actually do it, but you know.
Why wouldn't you? The amount of skin she shows?
Seriously? Dude, have we met?
She's got a point.
I mean, I love the heck out of Liz, but her mini pigtails are a problem.
They're what make her so adorable, but I couldn't pull them off.
Only little pixie-like girlies can rock that.
I'd go up in flames if I tried. Know what I mean?
Uh, what? Why the psycho stare? Is there something on my face?
I just... I was picturing it, and I think you'd look nice.
You honestly don't agree?
I mean, I know you didn't think you could cosplay Xiontan since she's a little kid,
but this is just a hairstyle, right?
Mm-hmm.
So why not go for it, then? Couldn't hurt to try.
Besides, you really seem to love her.
Um, I mean, I trust your judgment on these kinds of things.
S-so maybe for you.
You should.
Mm-hmm.
She really did look amazing as both Shizuku-tan and Black Lobelia,
so I know she doesn't have anything to worry about.
By the way, you said Liz was something called a succubus?
I've never heard that term.
Well, the short explanation is that they're lady demons.
Cool.
They make dudes have sexy time dreams,
and then they suck out all of their man juice and kill them.
In what world is that tranquil bedtime reading?
Yes, Gojo?
Would you say this one's more of a slice of seriously disturbed life?
Let me think.
No.
Next question.
Just read it.
It's peaceful.
How could a demon that kills you in your sleep be peaceful?
This is a relaxing escape.
Lullaby.
Hey!
Go to sleep already!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, mister!
I know.
I'll sing a lullaby so he'll get sleepy.
Rock-a-bye, baby, on the treetop.
I know who was a hale.
Chocolate.
You may be getting enough sleep at school,
but a backward sleep schedule is extremely bad for you.
Your autonomic nerves are gonna get all out of whack.
Now she decides to make sense.
Hey, succubus, I'll give you my midnight snack if you shut up.
Oh, really?
Thank you so much.
Yeah, you have milk filling, and they're super yummy.
I'm gonna go shanty's with the others.
You're right.
It does leave you with a warm, fuzzy feeling.
And she's so cute, doesn't it?
It's the best.
I knew you'd get it.
I'll be right back.
I'm gonna go grab some more books.
All right.
Slice of life.
I do get it.
It's nice.
Wait a minute.
This could be a problem.
The art style is cute and simplified.
How am I supposed to know how the clothes should drape?
There were parts I couldn't see on the other costumes,
but not to this extent.
I have no idea what the back looks like,
because it's always covered.
I see.
Depending on the series,
I may or may not be able to see the full details of the outfit.
I'll have to fill in the blanks and imagine them.
No way!
I didn't know it was sunset already.
Time flies.
We had such a lazy day today.
Yeah, I know.
But I had a lot of fun, though.
Yeah, me too.
Uh, Kitagawa?
Could we...
Huh?
Could we stop into a bookstore?
I really want to read Sakai DK.
Totally awesome, right?
I knew you'd get hooked.
I think there's one nearby.
Let's go.
There's also a clothing store.
You got some new Jinbei.
Perfect for this hot weather.
Good choice.
I actually got two sets.
This one looks great on you.
Grandpa, I...
I can't believe this.
It doesn't feel real.
I am currently at a love hotel.
The previous day.
I bought a swimsuit that looks like Liz's outfit,
and it's super cute.
I'm finished on my end as well.
For real?
Then you want to do Liz's photo shoot at a studio?
Your place is all Japanese style,
and the posters in my room are a bit yikes.
Hold up.
I found a studio that looks like Kaname's place,
and it's super close to you, Gojo.
Oh, damn!
It's only 5,900 yen.
It's so cheap.
I had no idea there was a photo studio near my house.
I reserved it so fast.
Can you meet me at the station tomorrow?
All right.
Are you sure there's really a studio in here?
Yeah, why not?
You got to pay first, so I'll go make that happen.
We're in room 303.
Wait.
They have more than 300 studios?
Here we are.
Oh, damn!
This bed is huge!
Like, everywhere size!
I mean, if you're a famous light novel author,
your bed better be this big!
There's so much room, but it's, like, simple, you know?
It looks just like Kaname's room!
Whoa!
OMG!
Is that what I think it is?
Yeah, dude.
Pretty sure we got a room in a love hotel.
Oh, well.
Whatever works.
What's the matter with you, bro?
Oh, uh, nothing at all.
It's just that far a second there.
I thought you said we're in a love hotel.
Yep.
Isn't it cool?
You didn't tell me that!
These are the things I'd like to be aware of!
Why are we in a love hotel?
Do you know what goes on in these places?
Not photography or in these...
I guess I got too excited.
I saw Kaname's bed online and just clicked.
It said we could take cosplay photos.
And it's stupid cheap!
So I insta-reserved, because hello!
And that brings us to now!
I didn't realize what it was until we were outside looking at the place.
And now we're locked in!
Sad emoji!
I guess it pays to read the fine print, huh?
Of course!
This is classic Kitaka!
But besides that, oopsie, I'd say we lucked out!
I mean, look around!
Is this not Toad's Kaname style?
I can make this work.
All I have to do is imagine it's a studio.
If only that were possible!
I'm not creative enough to ignore all of this!
The abandoned hospital I could deal with!
But I can't just pretend this stuff isn't here!
This room is crawling with adult paraphernalia!
I can't take it anymore!
I'm getting dizzy!
Just thinking about being in a love hotel with Kitagawa is more than I can handle!
To be honest, I've been curious about what these places are like.
I know some cosplayers who have sleepovers here.
And it sounds like a blast!
Girls' night at a love hotel?
Yeah!
See, doesn't that look rad?
You can even get a discount if you bring a large group!
I guess you're right.
They do look like they're having fun.
For sure!
Is that a bunch of bread underneath?
Yep!
I think they have it here, too!
Do you have a sweet tooth, Gojo?
Well, sometimes I eat candy.
But it's usually just when I'm working.
Chocolate's good when you're working on stuff that takes brain power.
That's why Kaname eats it so much.
Ah!
I was wondering why he was always eating those things.
Let's order some food!
Okay, thanks!
That actually sounds like a horrible idea!
That performance was a 10 out of 10.
Look, I know it was an honest mistake,
but we're both minors, so we're not even supposed to be in here!
Well, that might be true if we were normies.
What? We are normies!
Okay, fine, you win.
Sometimes my ideas suck.
Now that that's done, I'll go change!
What? Why?
Because the whole point was to cosplay!
It would be a huge waste of money if we didn't do it now, right?
Oh, you're serious.
Oh my god, look at this bathtub!
It's out of control!
Oh, it's a bougie jacuzzi, too!
Wanna hop in with me?
I'm totally kidding, dude!
Just sit back and chillax!
Nope! Can't do it!
Relaxation is not possible!
I agree that letting all that money go to waste
is not the ideal situation,
but still...
Chitagawa, please!
We have to go!
This is not good!
I'll just watch TV.
That should make the time go faster.
Stupid, pervy, love hotel!
We can't!
What kind of animal watch is this?
Oh my gosh!
I was just changing it!
I am freaking out!
This is the cutest one yet!
I am so hyped right now!
You are the best!
You really mean that?
I look super hot!
You are a for real genius!
The pearls for buttons are mega cute!
And I'm obsessed with the back of this collar being a heart!
It's ridiculously sweet!
It's also perfect!
I might throw up!
To make the collar,
I just matched the shape of Liz's tail.
I embellished with both chemical and cotton lace.
Oh, I've always wondered what that fabric was.
Also?
I, um, I did some research on the Succubi.
Since I was committed to making this,
I figured I should face the creatures head on.
You're hardcore, man.
They seem to be all about seduction.
I saw a lot of characters in, uh, revealing outfits,
but that's not the main focus of Succidee K.
So I made it more wholesome.
I'm so proud of you!
But then, I noticed her height changes.
So I imagined what the simplified portions would look like
if Liz were a real person,
and I ended up adding more details than I'd anticipated.
I guess it's my own interpretation.
If the goal was to match the author's design as closely as possible,
then technically, what I did would be wrong.
This totally works, though!
What?
Seriously.
It's like how designs change from manga to anime.
Oh, I didn't know that.
Mm-hmm.
Nothing wrong with cosplaying the anime if you like it better.
It's whatever floats your boat.
Cosplayers work hard on their outfits,
but in the end, they're all doing their own unique interpretation.
That's what makes it such an amazing hobby.
Being free to explore the world on your own terms makes it fun.
So this costume is your interpretation,
and that's totally the way to roll.
Besides, you can do no wrong.
Your cosplays are always flawless.
You do an incredible job.
You have to know that, right?
Oh, thank you so much.
Oh, that's right!
I heard this urban legend about how if you keep a condom in your wallet,
you'll get hella rich!
You want to try it?
I've never heard that before in my life!
I saw it on TV a while ago.
Cosplay is expensive,
so I could use some extra bread if you know what I mean.
Bingo!
Here's yours, Gojo.
Good luck!
Wait, I have to do it too?
Unless you want to be the worst friend ever!
Uh...
Huh?
How do the mini pigtails look?
Are they weird on me?
No, not at all.
You look like Liz just hopped out of the manga.
Really?
I feel so self-conscious right now.
Wow!
How beautiful!
What?
The wig!
The color is subtle, but still bright.
The wig?
I mean, it's cute, but what?
Uh...
Did I say something wrong?
Aw, yeah!
The instant I put on these fierce demon wings
is when this bad boy really starts to come to life.
I'm so hyped!
Okay.
I've been thinking,
and I want to recreate some scenes.
Yeah?
Like what?
I made sure to mark all my favorites.
It looks like you marked every page.
I even brought some props!
No way!
We're totally gonna get some baddie-bad photos with these!
Huh.
Your eyes are getting heavy,
and you're very sleepy.
Why didn't you warn me?
That would have been such a good shot!
Jeez, you're dramatic.
I can do it again, Goober.
Yes, that's perfect!
Hold it right there.
Oh, I love the mask!
It's so random, yet so Liz!
Let's get some shots of you eating chocolate.
Yeah, sounds good.
Can I have another one?
Kitagawa?
So good!
I think that's good, Kitagawa.
I promise we've got plenty of shots with the chocolate.
We took so many photos!
We sure did!
Okay, last one.
I wanted to get a shot of her singing the lullaby to him.
Oh, for sure!
That scene is a huge must!
Let's take it right now!
Great!
We're on the same page!
Oh my god, you hate it.
I don't hate it, but something's definitely not right.
We need to see the eye contact, but I'm not quite sure how.
So you want it like Liz is looking at the viewer?
Oh, that's it!
Kitagawa, think you can get on top of me?
The lens can be Kahneman's point of view.
What if you can't breathe?
Is that safe?
I'll take it quickly.
It'll be fine.
Well, if you're sure.
If I'm too heavy, just tell me, okay?
I will, but you're not.
I'm gonna sit down, so brace yourself.
I'm braced.
Ready?
Tighten your abs.
Good to go whenever you are.
I'm gonna start shooting.
Okay.
That's so good!
I know!
Like perfection!
It's amazing what a difference the angle can make.
Don't stop.
It's so fun!
I love getting ready and seeing the gorgeous cosplay come to life, and then taking the photos
and looking at them together.
It's just the best!
I can't think of one thing I don't love to death about cosplay!
There's nothing better in the whole world!
That's great!
I'm having fun shooting with you!
I just heard a voice coming from next door.
It sounded like...
Oh, God!
I totally forgot!
I'm in a love hotel!
What have I done?
I was so caught up in the photoshoot!
I told Kitsukawa to get on top of me!
And she did!
Huh?
Kitsukawa!
I need you to get off of me right now!
Ah!
Huh?
Huh
Hello, Kojo dolls, how may I help you?
I mean, sorry. Excuse me? An extension of what? Oh, no, no, no, that's okay. Yes, I'm quite sure, thank you.
Apparently someone else needs this room.
Oh, right. Okay, I guess I lost track of time. I'm gonna go change now.
That was way too close.
Sorry, you go ahead.
Oh, my goodness. How old are we? High schoolers, maybe? That's adorable.
Looking for a little summertime thrill. I remember being that age and eager to learn all about these places.
What have you done?
Oh, my goodness.
See you next time.